A Guide to the Documents from the County Manager's Library, 1889-1994
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
- Budget and Finance
  - Budgets, County (listed by fiscal year)
    - Proposed, 1949 (Box 74)
    - Revenues & Expenditures, 1950 (Box 74)
    - Proposed (added pencil notes), 1950 (Box 75)
    - Proposed, 1950 (Box 75)
    - Proposed, 1951 (Box 75)
    - Adopted, 1951 (Box 75)
    - Summary & Analysis, 1951 (Box 75)
    - Proposed, 1952 (1) (Box 75)
    - Proposed, 1952 (2) (Box 75)
    - Proposed, 1952 (3) (Box 75)
    - Proposed, 1952 (4) (Box 76)
    - Proposed Draft, 1952 (Box 76)
    - Adopted, 1952 (1) (Box 76)
    - Adopted, 1952 (2) (Box 76)
    - Adopted, 1952 (3) (Box 76)
    - Adopted, 1952 (4) (Box 76)
    - Proposed, Detail of Expenditures, 1953 (Box 76)
    - Budget Summary, 1952-1953 (Box 76)
    - Proposed, 1954 (Box 76)
    - Proposed, Detail of Expenditures, 1955 (Box 100)
    - Proposed, Detail of Expenditures, Maintenance and Operations in General and Operating Funds, 1955-1956 (Box 77)
    - Propsed, Summary, 1955-1956 (Box 77)
    - Proposed, Detail of Expenditures, 1957 (Box 77)
    - Proposed, General/Special/Capital/School Budget, 1957 (Box 77)
    - Summary, 1956-1957 (Box 77)
    - Proposed, Detail of Expenditures, 1958 (Box 77)
    - Schools, 1958 (Box 77)
    - Proposed, Summary, 1962 (Box 77)
    - Proposed, Summary, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Two-Year Budget Projection, 1966-1967 (Box 77)
    - Budget Message, "Emerging Horizons," 1969 (Box 77)
    - Proposed, Budget Message, Summary, 1978 (Box 77)
    - Budget Message, Summary, 1982 (Box 77)
    - Budget Message, Summary, 1983 (Box 77)
    - Charts, Revenues & Expenditure, 1932-1947 (Box 77)
  - Annual Financial Reports
    - 1955 (FY) (Box 78)
    - 1976 (Box 78)
    - 1978 (Box 78)
    - 1980 (Box 78)
    - 1981 (Box 78)
    - 1982 (Box 78)
    - 1984 (Box 78)
    - Reports on Finances (summaries), 1938-1959 (Box 78)
  - Operating Instructions
    - Manual of Standard Practice, Director of Finance, 1950 (Box 78)
    - Manual of Standard Practice, 1952 (Box 78)
    - Manual of Standard Practice, 1958 (Box 78)
    - Manual of Standard Practice, 1965 (Box 78)
    - Manual of Standard Practice, 1969 (Box 78)
    - Classification/Codification of Accounts, 1941 (Box 79)
    - Classification/Codification, 1945 (Box 79)
    - Present Procedures: Purchasing, Contract Letting, Sales, 1951 (Box 79)
    - Handling Money - Policies, Procedures, 1953 (Box 79)
    - Purchasing Manual, 1954 (Box 79)
    - Purchasing Manual, 1967 (Box 79)
    - Purchasing Manual, 1976, with instructions, 1981 (Box 79)
    - Accounting Manual, 1959 (Box 79)
    - County Budget Manual, 1934 (OVERSIZE) (Box 79)
  - Fiscal Affairs Advisory Committee
    - Report FY 1972 Budget (Box 79)
    - Report FY 1973 (Box 79)
    - Report FY 1974 (Box 79)
    - Report FY 1975 (Box 79)
- Court Cases
  - Cab Service: Arlington Yellow Cab vs. Transportation Inc.
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of VA, Appellees' Brief, 1966 (Box 79)
  - Desegregation: Hoffman-Boston Jr High School
    - U.S. Court of Appeals, Fourth Circuit, Decision, 1966 (Box 79)
  - Drowning Accident at Sewer Construction Site
    - Supreme Court of Appeals, Trial Record, 1957 (Box 80)
  - Federal Employees holding State/County Office
    - Circuit Court of Arlington County, Opinion, 1952 (Box 80)
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of VA, Petitioner's Brief, 1952 (Box 80)
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of VA, Memorandum Brief, 1952 (Box 80)
    - Circuit Court of Arlington County, Opinion, 1952 (Box 80)
  - Fire Fighting Equipment, payment for
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of VA, Petition, 1936 (Box 80)
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of VA, Defendant's Brief, 1937 (Box 80)
  - Incinerating Plant Bids
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of VA, Trial Record, 1948 (Box 80)
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of VA, Defendant's Brief, 1948 (Box 80)
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of VA, Opinion, 1949 (Box 80)
  - Real Estate Assessment
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of VA, Plaintiff's Brief, 1951 (Box 80)
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of VA, Defendant's Brief, 1951 (Box 80)
    - Circuit Court of Arlington, Opinion, 1952 (Box 80)
  - Wharf Construction in Potomac River
    - U.S. Supreme Court, Opinion, 1933 (Box 80)
  - Zoning: Cherrydale Cement Block Company
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of VA, Appellees' Brief, 1930 (Box 80)
- Environmental Affairs, Planning Division - Clippings (looseleaf notebooks)
  - Clippings by Year
    - 1935-1951 (1) (Box 80)
    - 1935-1951 (2) (Box 80)
    - 1952-1954 (1) (Box 80)
    - 1952-1954 (2) (Box 81)
    - 1952-1954 (3) (Box 81)
    - 1955 (1) (Box 81)
    - 1955 (2) (Box 81)
    - 1955 (3) (Box 81)
    - 1956-1957 (1) (Box 81)
    - 1956-1957 (2) (Box 81)
    - 1956-1957 (3) (Box 81)
    - 1957-1958 (1) (Box 81)
    - 1957-1958 (2) (Box 81)
    - 1957-1958 (3) (Box 81)
    - 1958-1959 (1) (Box 81)
    - 1958-1959 (2) (Box 81)
    - 1958-1959 (3) (Box 81)
    - 1960 (1) (Box 81)
    - 1960 (2) (Box 82)
    - 1961-1963 (1) (Box 82)
    - 1961-1963 (2) (Box 82)
    - 1961-1963 (3) (Box 82)
    - 1961-1963 (4) (Box 82)
    - 1964 (1) (Box 82)
    - 1964 (2) (Box 82)
    - 1964 (3) (Box 82)
    - 1964 (4) (Box 82)
    - 1965-1966 (1) (Box 82)
    - 1965-1966 (2) (Box 82)
    - 1965-1966 (3) (Box 82)
    - 1965-1966 (4) (Box 82)
    - 1965-1966 (5) (Box 83)
    - 1966-1967 (1) (Box 83)
    - 1966-1967 (2) (Box 83)
    - 1966-1967 (3) (Box 83)
    - 1966-1967 (4) (Box 83)
    - 1968 (1) (Box 83)
    - 1968 (2) (Box 83)
    - 1968 (3) (Box 83)
    - 1969 (1) (Box 83)
    - 1969 (2) (Box 83)
    - 1969 (3) (Box 83)
    - 1969 (4) (Box 83)
    - 1970 (1) (Box 83)
    - 1970 (2) (Box 83)
    - 1970 (3) (Box 83)
    - 1970 (4) (Box 84)
    - 1971 (1) (Box 84)
    - 1971 (2) (Box 84)
  - Clippings by Subject
    - The Elderly (Box 84)
    - Nursing Homes (Box 84)
    - LRCIP Long Range Improvement (Box 84)
    - Condominiums and Townhouses (Box 84)
    - Transportation (Box 84)
    - County Board and Other Members (Box 84)
    - Parking (Box 84)
    - Jefferson Davis/Route 1 Corridor (Box 84)
    - Environment (Box 84)
    - Highways (Box 84)
    - Mass Transit (Box 84)
- 1966 Arrangement of County Manager's Documents
  - Documents Collection Main Entry List, 1966 (Box 84)
  - Reference: A Library Classification for Public Administration Materials, Sophia Hall Glidden, 1942 (Box 84)
  - Thesis: A Proposed Plan for the Organization and Administration of a Reference Library for the County Manager Government of Arlington, Virginia, Marcel Raymond Gerin, The Catholic University, 1959 (Box 84)
- Advisory Groups
  - Advisory Group Listings
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1954 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1956 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1957 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1958 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1959 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1960 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1961 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1963 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1964 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1966 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1968 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1969 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1970 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1971-1972 (Box 85)
    - "Boards, Committees, and Commissions of Arlington County," 1974 (Box 85)
    - Advisory Groups, 1975 (Box 85)
    - Advisory Groups, 1976 (Box 85)
    - Advisory Groups, 1977 (Box 85)
    - Advisory Groups, 1980 (Box 85)
    - Advisory Groups, 1981 (1) (Box 85)
    - Advisory Groups, 1981 (2) (Box 85)
    - Advisory Groups, 1982 (Box 85)
    - Citizens on Committees, County Board name list 1960 (Box 86)
  - Budget & Finance
    - Business and Professional License Tax in Arlington, Advisory Committee on Fiscal Affairs, 1951 (Box 86)
    - Interim Budget Committee Report, 1954 (Box 86)
  - Civil Service
    - Civil Service Commission Minutes and Agendas, 1973 (Box 86)
    - Civil Service Commission Minutes and Agendas, 1974 (Box 86)
    - Civil Service Commission Minutes and Agendas, 1975 (Box 86)
    - Civil Service Commission Minutes and Agendas, 1976 (Box 86)
    - Civil Service Commission Minutes and Agendas, 1977 (Box 86)
    - Civil Service Commission Minutes and Agendas, 1978 (Box 86)
    - Civil Service Commission Minutes and Agendas, 1979 (Box 86)
    - Civil Service Commission Minutes and Agendas, 1980 (Box 86)
    - Civil Service Commission Minutes and Agendas, 1981 (Box 86)
    - Civil Service Commission Minutes and Agendas, 1982 (Box 86)
    - Board of Trustees, Supplemental Retirement System, minutes, 1976-1982 (scattered) (Box 109)
  - Consumer Protection
    - Consumer Protection Commission Annual Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 86)
    - Consumer Protection Commission Annual Reports, 1973 (Box 86)
    - Consumer Protection Commission Annual Reports, 1974 (Box 86)
    - Consumer Protect Commission minutes, membership, etc., 1971-1974 (Box 86)
    - Consumer Arbitration Rules, Consumer Protection Commission, 1972 (Box 86)
    - Help Balance Your Scale of Living, leaflet, Consumer Affairs Commission, n.d. (Box 86)
  - County Government
    - Incorporation of Arlington under 1946 Charter, Citizens Study Commission on Local Government, Report #3, 1952 (Box 86)
    - Report to Citizens, Commission on Incorporation, 1958 (Box 86)
    - Commission on Incorporation, Final Report & Proposed Charter, 1959 (Box 86)
    - Study Commission of City/County Form of Government, Preliminary Report, 1979 (Box 86)
    - Study Commission, Final Report, 1979 (Box 87)
    - Improving Local Government, Ad Hoc Committee Report, 1981 (Box 87)
  - Criminal Justice
    - Physical Security Guidelines, draft (no date), Criminal Justice Advisory Commission (Box 87)
    - Police Advisory Committee Report, 1968 (Box 87)
    - Criminal Justice Advisory Committee, correspondence, minutes, etc., 1975-1979 (Box 87)
    - Survey of Victims & Witnesses of Felony Crimes in Arlington County, Criminal Justice Advisory Committee, 1978 (Box 87)
  - Drug Abuse
    - Citizens' Advisory Committee, Drug Abuse Program, 1974-1975 (Box 87)
  - Ethics
    - Citizens' Committee on Ethics in Government, Report, 1952 (Box 87)
  - Environment
    - Environmental Quality 1972, Annual Report, Environmental Improvement Commission (Box 87)
    - Environmental Imrpovement Commission, 1973 (Box 87)
    - Environmental Imrpovement Commission, 1974 (Box 87)
    - Environmental Imrpovement Commission, 1975 (Box 87)
    - Environmental Imrpovement Commission, 1976 (Box 87)
    - Environmental Imrpovement Commission, 1977 (Box 87)
    - Beautification Committee, 1965 (Box 87)
    - Beautification Committee, 1966 (Box 87)
    - Beautification Committee, 1967 (Box 87)
    - Beautification Committee, 1969 (Box 87)
    - Beautification Committee, 1975, 1977, 1978, 1983 (Box 87)
  - Growth
    - Problems of Growth in Arlington, Arlington Committee on Optimum Growth, 1971 (Box 87)
    - Arlington Growth Patterns Committee, minutes, Sep 1973 (Box 87)
    - Rosslyn-Ballston Corridor, Citizens' View, Arlington Committee on Optimum Growth, 1973 (Box 87)
  - Housing
    - Housing Needs, Arlington Community Action Committee, 1966 (Box 88)
    - Housing Advisory Committee, First Annual Report, 1972 (Box 88)
    - Tenant-Landlord Commission, minutes, tenant info, etc., 1974, 1975, 1977-1980 (Box 88)
    - Tenant-Landlord Commission, 1981-1983 (Box 88)
    - References: Housing Standards Ordincance, 1972; Absentee Landlord Law, 1973 (Resident Agent Section (Box 88)
  - History
    - Cultural Heritage Commission Recommendations, 1964 (Box 88)
    - Historical Affairs & Landmark Review Board, Annual Report, 1987 (Box 88)
  - Human Resources
    - Directory of Resources, Community Council, 1947 (Box 88)
    - Community Resources Directory, Arlington Community Chest & Council, 1949 (Box 88)
    - Advisory Committee on Public Welfare, Report, 1961 (Box 88)
    - Arlington's Low Income Families (Working Poor and Elderly), Health & Welfare Council, 1969 (Box 88)
    - School Health Services, Ad Hoc Committee, minutes, 1974 (Box 88)
    - Human Services Integration, Ad Hoc Committee, hearing, press release, clippings, 1975 (Box 88)
    - Human Resources Commission Agenda, April 1976 (Box 88)
    - Advisory Committee on Health & Welfare, Report, County Board responses (no date) (Box 88)
    - Arlington Community Mental Health & Mental Retardation Services Board, minutes, notes, etc., 1976-1979 (Box 88)
    - Commission on Aging, Agendas, Minutes, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 88)
    - Commission on Aging, Agendas, Minutes, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 88)
    - Commission on Aging, Agendas, Minutes, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 88)
    - Commission on Aging, Agendas, Minutes, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 88)
    - Commission on Aging, Agendas, Minutes, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 88)
    - Commission on Aging, Agendas, Minutes, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 88)
  - Manpower
    - Manpower Planning Council, 1974-1978 (Box 88)
    - Manpower Planning Council, 1979 (Box 89)
    - Manpower Planning Council, 1980 (Box 89)
    - Manpower Planning Council, 1981 (Box 89)
    - Manpower Planning Council, 1982 (Box 89)
  - Neighborhood Services
    - Community Council, First Annual Report, 1946 (Box 89)
    - Arlington Arts Center, Ad Hoc Advisory Committee, 1968 (Box 89)
    - Neighborhood Services Study Committee, Report, 1972 (Box 89)
  - Parks and Recreation
    - Parks and Recreation Commission, 1974-1979 (scattered) (Box 89)
    - Open Space in Rosslyn-Ballston Corridor, Park & Recreation Committee, 1984 (Box 89)
  - Pentagon City
    - Pentagon City Coordinating Committee Response to Rezoning Application, 1976 (1) (Box 89)
    - Pentagon City Coordinating Committee Response to Rezoning Application, 1976 (2) (Box 89)
    - Pentagon City Coordinating Committee Response to Rezoning Application, 1976 (3) (Box 89)
  - Planning
    - Six-Year Plan, Prelim Report, Planning Committee, 1950 (Box 89)
    - Arlington Catches Up!, Six Year Improvement Program, Arlington. County Planning Commission, 1951 (Box 89)
    - Planning Commission Annual Report, 1951 (Box 89)
    - Arlington Looks Ahead, Six-Year Improvement Program, Planning Committee, 1951 (Box 89)
    - Arlington Looks Ahead, Supplement 1, Arlington Development Committee, 1953 (Box 89)
    - Master Plan Work Program approval, Planning Committee, 1956 (Box 89)
    - Prospectus & Work Program...Arlington Development Committee, 1956 (Box 89)
    - Critical Choices, rough draft, Committee on Long-Range County Improvement Program, 1975 (Box 90)
    - Critical Choices, final draft (from the above) (Box 90)
  - Public Utilities
    - Public Utilities Commission Annual Report, 1934 (Box 90)
    - Public Utilities Commission Annual Reports, 1947-1955 (Box 90)
    - Public Utilities Commission Annual Reports, 1956-1960 (Box 90)
    - Public Utilities Commission Annual Reports, 1961-1965 (Box 90)
    - Water Resources Citizen Advisory Committee, Recommendations on Draft 208 Plan, 1978 (Box 90)
    - Water Needs, Ad Hoc Committee Report, 1980 (Box 90)
  - Rosslyn
    - Rosslyn Committee Report, 1978 (Box 90)
  - Transportation
    - Citizens' Action Committee on I-66, report, 1958 (Box 90)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, Nat Airport, background info, 1979-1983 (scattered) (Box 90)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, Nat Airport, Industry Reports, various, 1980-1983 (Box 91)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, National Airport, Government Agency Reports, various, 1977-1983 (Box 91)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, National Airport, correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 91)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, National Airport, minutes, agendas, 1983-1984 (Box 91)
  - Urban Renewal
    - Urban Renewal Referendum, Ad Hoc Committee Report, 1961 (Box 91)
  - Women
    - Committee on Status of Women, Report, 1974 (Box 91)
    - Committee on Status of Women, minutes, pub hearing, 1973 (Box 91)
    - Committee on Status of Women, minutes, Mar 1974 (Box 91)
  - Zoning
    - Public Notices, Board of Zoning Appeals, 1972 (Box 91)
    - Public Notices, Board of Zoning Appeals, 1973 (Box 91)
    - Public Notices, Board of Zoning Appeals, 1974 (Box 91)
    - Public Notices, Board of Zoning Appeals, 1975 (Box 91)
    - Public Notices, Board of Zoning Appeals, 1976 (Box 91)
    - Public Notices, Board of Zoning Appeals, 1977 (Box 91)
    - Public Notices, Board of Zoning Appeals, 1978 (Box 91)
    - Public Notices, Board of Zoning Appeals, 1979 (Box 91)
    - Public Notices, Board of Zoning Appeals, 1980 (Box 91)
- Arlington County Civic Federation
  - Schools Committee
    - Agenda, Patrick Henry PTA, November 1945 (Box 91)
    - Bond Issue, Background, 1952 (Box 91)
    - School Operating Budget, 1952-1953 (Box 91)
    - School Budget, School Board's Estimate, 1952-1953 (Box 91)
    - Uncovering Hidden Numbers...School & Out-of-School Number Experiences, Arlington County Schools, 1953 (Box 91)
    - What About Reading? Fact List, Arlington County Schools, 1953-1954 (Box 91)
    - Water Restrictions, flyer, Department of Public Service, Water Division, 1954 (Box 91)
    - Student Body & Faculty Profile, Northern Virginia University Center, 1954 (Box 91)
    - "Facts Concerning Segregation and Integration," Arlington County School Board, November-December, 1954 (Box 91)
    - Mental Health in Virginia, Quarterly, Virginia Department of Mental Hygiene & Hospitals, Autumn, 1954 (Box 91)
    - Arlington Civic Federation Bulletin, 1954, 1955 (scattered) (Box 91)
    - School Budget, Proposed, 1954-1955, with Report of Salary Committee, Arlington Education Association, 1954 (Box 91)
    - Statistics, Committee Assignments, news clips, 1954-1955 (Box 91)
    - School Budget, Proposed, 1955-1956 (Box 91)
    - Bonds, County & School, Voter Information, 1971 (Box 92)
    - Planning Regulations, County, pamphlets (Box 92)
    - Office Building Directory, with news clip of Rosslyn development, 1980 (Box 92)
    - Expansion of NOVA University Center, report, (no date) (Box 92)
    - Broyhill campaign brochure (no date) (Box 92)
    - Information for Committee Chairmen, Arlington County Civic Federation (no date) (Box 92)
    - Miscellaneous: information on schools, 1950s-1960s (scattered) (Box 92)
    - Elections: informational materials, 1950s-1960s (scattered) (Box 92)
    - Miscellaneous: information on various civic organizations, 1950s-1980s (scattered) (Box 92)
- Photographs
  - Subgroup 1, Series 61, File 4:
    - Zoning Proposals at Arlington Towers, 1957 (10 photos)
      - Key Bridge, Roosevelt Island, aerial (Box 93)
      - Iwo Jima Memorial, aerial (Box 93)
      - Vacant lot, Memorial Bridge, Lincoln Memorial and Washington Monument in background (Box 93)
      - Lumber yard, Arlington Asphalt (Box 93)
      - Chevrolet Truck billboards, Cities Service building to right (Box 93)
      - Supermarket, laundry, J. A. Laporte Construction Company, Key Bridge (Box 93)
      - Industrial area, Route 50 middle left, Post Office building to right (Box 93)
      - Rucker Lumber Company, Dyer Brothers, O'Brien & Rohall Mercury in background (Box 93)
      - Post Office, Rucker Lumber Company (Box 93)
      - Dyer Brothers, mid-left, Stewart Buick, far-right (2 copies) N* (Box 93)
  - Subgroup 4, Series 11, File 12:
    - Arlington Hospital Information Kit, 1979 (2 photos)
      - Hospital from street, garage (Box 93)
      - Hospital from street, two light poles (Box 93)
  - Subgroup 7, Series 2, File 3:
    - Coaster Car Race, August 1949 (4 photos)
      - Starting flag, Cars #104, 106 (Box 93)
      - Starting flag, Cars #103, 107 (Box 93)
      - Starting flag, Cars #111, 116 (?) (Box 93)
      - Finish line, 2 cars, unidentified (Box 93)
  - Subgroup 7, Series 7, File 17:
    - Storm Drain, Proposed, & Landscape Plan, George Mason Drive, 1949. Eight photos of open storm drain prior to construction
      - Open drain, old tire and other trash in ditch (Box 93)
      - Culverts, wooden guard rail (Box 93)
      - Open drain, two boys playing in ditch, man in overcoat, top left (Box 93)
      - Culvert opening, two boys playing in ditch (Box 93)
      - Open drain, two boys running along street to left (Box 93)
      - Culvert & open drain, guard rail at bottom edge (Box 93)
      - Culvert & open drain, showing more of street and houses (Box 93)
      - Open drain, snow scene (Box 93)
  - Subgroup 7, Series 8, File 1:
    - Fire Insurance Survey, Schools, 1932 (24 photos)
      - Ballston (old building) (Box 93)
      - Barcroft (Box 93)
      - Cherrydale (old building) (Box 93)
      - Cherrydale (new building) (Box 93)
      - Glencarlyn (Box 93)
      - Henry Clay (Box 93)
      - Hume (Box 93)
      - James Monroe (Box 93)
      - Jefferson Annex (colored) (Box 93)
      - Jefferson Main (colored) (Box 93)
      - John M. Langston (colored) (Box 93)
      - John Marshall (Box 93)
      - Kemper (Box 93)
      - Matthew F. Maury (Box 93)
      - Nellie Custis (Box 93)
      - Patrick Henry (Box 93)
      - Robert E. Lee (Box 93)
      - Saegmuller (Box 93)
      - Stonewall Jackson (Box 93)
      - Thomas Nelson Page (Box 93)
      - Washington-Lee (Box 93)
      - Washington-Lee Manual Training Building (Box 93)
      - Woodmont (Box 93)
      - Woodrow Wilson (Box 93)
  - Subgroup 7, Series 8, File 2:
    - Fire Insurance Survey, Various County Properties, 1932 (15 photos) (2 copies of #0170)
      - Bungalow (Box 93)
      - Clarendon Health Center (Box 93)
      - Cherrydale Health Center (Box 93)
      - Clerk's Office (Box 93)
      - Farm Kennels (Box 93)
      - Farm Main Barn (Box 93)
      - Farm Main Garage (Box 93)
      - Farm Office (Box 93)
      - Old Blacksmith Shop (Box 93)
      - Farm Repair Shop (Box 93)
      - Court House (Box 93)
      - Jail (Box 93)
      - New Blacksmith Shop (Box 93)
      - Virginia Highlands Health Center (Box 93)
  - Subgroup 7, Series 2, File 9:
    - Swimming Program (4 photos, no documentation); children being bussed to public pools in Washington DC
      - Children boarding bus (Box 93)
      - Children waiting at pool entrance (Box 93)
      - Poolside, 4 girls on diving board (Box 93)
      - Poolside, general view of swimmers (Box 93)
- BOX 94
  - Annual Report, 1948-1949
  - Annual Report, 1949-1950
  - Annual Report, 1951-1952
  - Annual Report, 1952-1953
  - Annual Report, 1953-1954
  - Annual Report, 1954-1955
  - Annual Report, 1955-1956
- BOX 95
  - Annual Report, 1956-1957
  - Annual Report, 1957-1958
  - Annual Report, 1958-1959
  - Annual Report, 1959-1960
  - Annual Report, 1962-1963
- BOX 96
  - Annual Report, 1964-1965
  - Annual Report, 1965-1966
  - Annual Report, 1966-1967
  - Proposed Budget, 1951-1952
  - General Fund, School and Special Fund Budgets, 1952-1953
  - General Fund, Special Funds, and Capital Budget, 1953-1954
  - Budget, 1954-1955
  - Buddget, 1955-1956
  - Detail of Expenditures for Maintenance and Operations in General and Operating Funds, 1956-1957
  - Adopted Budgets: General Fund Special Funds, Capital Budget, 1957-1958
- BOX 97
  - Adopted Budget: General Fund, Special Funds, and Capital Budget, 1956-1957
  - Annual Budget, 1958-1959
  - Annual Budget, 1959-1960
  - Annual Budget, 1960-1961
  - Arlington County Budget, 1961-1962
  - Arlington County Budget, 1962-1963
  - Arlington County Budget, 1963-1964
  - Arlington County Budget, 1964-1965
  - Arlington County Budget, 1965-1966
  - Arlington County Budget, 1966-1967